>> Jem Young: 要完成 HP 部分，我们花费了一段时间。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: To finish off the HP
section, we spent a while on it.
真是太好了
That's pretty rewarding.
我们现在有一个在 SSL 和 HP/2 上运行的现代化网站，你在想，
We now have a modern site running on
SSL and HP/2 and you're thinking,
太棒了但  很快就会出来了
that's great, but
HTTP/3 is coming out soon, too.
我觉得我刚弄明白了
I feel like I just figured out HTTP/2.
没事的没事的
It's okay.
这是 HTTP/3。
Here's HTTP/3.
已退出。
HTTP/3 is out.
但我说出去
But I say out.
互联网在滚动的过程中非常缓慢。
The internet's pretty slow in
terms of rolling things out.
例如，现在只有 42% 的互联网使用
For instance, only about 42% of
the internet uses HTTP/2 now,
尽管它已经被淘汰了好几年了
even though it's been out for years now.
这是一个非常缓慢的进展。
It's a very slow progress.
我指责银行和公司，他们是，我们会去的。
I blame banks and corporations,
they're, yeah we'll get to it.
但是当您运行大量用户的大型服务器时，添加
But when you're running a large server
with thousands of users, adding HTTP/2,
添加 SSL 并不像我们在这里所做的那么简单，而且它会花费金钱。
adding SSL is not as easy as we made
it here, and it does cost money.
你会增加你的服务器时间之类的
You're gonna increase your server time and
things like that.
但是，及时地让人们不再采用  。
But just in time for people not to
adopt HTTP/2, HTTP/3 comes out.
HTTP/2 与
The difference between HTTP/2 and
是所有前代 HTTP 奖励中的  。
HTTP/3 is HTTP/2 in all previous
generations of HTTP bonus.
我今天说过多少次了
How many times did I say HTTP today?
这么多
So many.
但在过去的几代，它们都是通过 TCP运行的。
But all the previous generations,
they all run over TCP.
请记住，它仍然是握手协议，而  使其更快
Remember that it is still that handshake
protocol, while HTTP/2 made it faster
因为我们多路复用了这一点，所以我们每次都不握手。
because we multiplex that so we are not
doing a handshake every single time.
这样做还需要付出代价。
There is still a cost to doing that.
他们还在压缩或者
And they are still doing
that compression or
他们还在进行纠错
they are still doing
that error correction.
因此，如果我们想回到我们早先关于 TCP的教训。
So if we think back to our
earlier lesson about TCP.
TCP 错误更正，因此如果缺少任何包，那么它表示，嘿，一，二，三，
TCP error corrects, so if any packets are
missing, it says, hey, one, two ,three,
四，五，六，七失踪。
four, five, but six and seven are missing.
您将该请求发送至服务器和服务器，我的错误。
And you send that request to
the server and the server's, my bad.
让我再发一次
Let me send those again.
这就是 TCP 可靠的原因是必要的
And that's what makes TCP reliable and
it was something that was necessary,
尤其是在网络的早期连接会下降的时候
especially back in the early days of
the internet when connections would drop.
特别是当我们使用拨号时，它非常容易连接。
Especially when we're using dial up,
which is very prone to lossy connection.
我不知道你有没有用过拨号码再跟我自己约会
I don't know if any of you ever
use dial up, dating myself again.
但我不知道你是否知道下载 mp3 的痛苦
But I don't know if you know the pain
of downloading an mp3 you're, yeah,
是新的我不知道谁受欢迎
it's the new, I don't know who's popular..
182 条可能是正确的时间对吧
Blink 182 that was probably that's
about the right time, right?
我在 56K 调制解调器上花了一个小时的下载 Blink 182 。
I spent an hour downloading Blink
182 one song over my 56k modem.
然后有人打个招呼，你就输了。
And then someone picks up the phone
like hello, and you lose it all.
是的，网络连接的旧日是靠不住的，所以
And yes, the old days of the internet
connections were unreliable, so
我们需要有很多纠错的东西
we needed something with
a lot of error correction.
现在互联网的可靠性更高得多
Now, the internet's much more reliable,
it's much more of a staple,
就像一条电源线，或者你的水位线之类的。
kind of like a power line, or
your water line or something like that.
谷歌做了什么，他们发明了一种新的协议，
So, what Google did,
was they invented a new protocol called,
快速 UDP 连接。
Quick UDP Connections.
因此，我们现在使用基于 UDP的 HTTP 而不是基于 HTTP 的 HTTP 。
So instead of HTTP over TCP,
we now have HTTP over UDP.
从我们早先的经验
And from our earlier lessons,
记得 UDP 更有爆炸的地方，中共就是，你拿到了吗 ?
remember that UDP is more of a blast,
where CCP is, hey did you get it?
他就像我一样
He's like yeah I got it.
UDP 是我要把你的数据发给你
UDP is I'm gonna send you data and
assuming you got it.
它有一些纠错的内置，但是因为网络更可靠，
And it has some error correction built in,
but because the internet's more reliable,
我们就快得快得多了
it's much faster cuz we don't
have to do that handshake of sin
承认和所有这些东西都是 UDP 爆炸的
in acts in acknowledge and
all these other things UDP just blasts.
如果您想检查任何支持 UDP 的内容
If you wanna check if
anything supporting UDP
用更快的 HTTP/3 ，我们可以把 Gmail 拉上来。
using quicker HTTP/3,
we can actually pull up a Gmail.
我不会把我的 Gmail cuz 拉到我的邮件里
I won't pull my Gmail cuz that's my mail.
但如果你打开你的 Gmail 或谷歌自己的财产
But if you open your Gmail or
something Google own property,
你会在协议中看到它现在说的是 HTTP/quick 46
you'll see in the protocol
it now says HTTP/quick 46.
那是因为 HTTP/3 不太正式。
That's because HTTP/3
is not quite official.
它不像所有浏览器都支持的那样。
It's not like well supported
by all the browsers.
但是我们现在还不能实现这个
But we, we can't implement this yet
因为它不太受支持
because it's not really
being supported too much.
我都不认为 NGINX 是支持它的，我知道， Sam，你知道吗 ?
I don't even think NGINX supports
it far as I know, Sam, do you know?
> > Sam: 否，不离我的头。
&gt;&gt; Sam: No, not off the top of my head.
我知道灯塔绝对支持
I know that Lighthouse
definitely supports it.
>> Jem Young: 真的吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Really?
那就有道理了
That makes sense.
这也是谷歌拥有的产品。
That's a Google owned product as well.
Google 和 Cloudflare 现在支持 。
Google and Cloudflare now support HTTP/3.
我们会看到逐渐采用的方式
We'll see gradual adoption, but
这又是你在未来五年里看到的。
this is again something you'll
see in the next five years or so.
它确实创造了一个 13 岁的婴儿
And it does create a baby 13,
it depends on the connection,
但如在 HTTP/2 上增加 13 % 到 20% 的速度
but say like 13 to 20% speed
increase over HTTP/2 which
很令人印象深刻因为你认为速度比 HTTP/1 加速
is pretty impressive because you think
that speed increase over HTTP/1, we're
只需配置我们发送数据的方式就能更快地实现 50% 的增长。
talking up to 50% faster just from just
configuring the way we're sending data.
太棒了
That's pretty awesome.
我不知道你的事但那很酷
I don't know about you,
but that's pretty cool.
可能是完整堆栈的 V3 或
Maybe in version three of full-stack or
前端将能够实现 。
front-end will be able
to implement HTTP/3.